http://www.taoofwellness.com/privacy

Schedule An Appointment
Privacy IntroductionTao of Wellness, a company incorporated under the laws of the State of California, U.S.A., (referred to herein as “Tao of Wellness,” “we,” “us” and “our”) understands the importance of privacy of individuals (referred to as “users” and “you”). Tao of Wellness, may also maintains websites for several affiliate companies and brands. This privacy notice outlines the personal information Tao of Wellness may collect and how Tao of Wellness will use and disclose that information. Tao of Wellness is committed to protecting your personal information. We have adopted the following policies with regard to collection and distribution of information.Information CollectionTao of Wellness may collect two different types of information, Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. “Personally Identifiable Information” (“PII”) is information that identifies you as an individual – for example, your name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, billing address and shipping information. “Non-Personally Identifiable Information” (“Non-PII”) is aggregated information, demographic information, IP addresses, user behavior data from web interaction metrics tools and any other information that does not reveal your specific identity.During the enrollment process, or while purchasing products on Tao of Wellness maintained websites, Tao of Wellness may collect PII about you that may be considered sensitive. Tao of Wellness may also collect PII about you from, among other places: information you provide directly to us, information regarding the services that Tao of Wellness currently provides or has previously provided to you, information Tao of Wellness receives from our affiliated entities or third parties relating to the establishment of our relationship or the provision of services to you.This information can be received in any manner, including in-person discussions, telephone conversations, and electronic or other written communications.CookiesWe may collect information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us to estimate our audience size and usage pattern, to store information about your preferences (and so allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests), to speed up your searches and to recognize you when you return to our site. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site. Information UseTao of Wellness may collect PII about you to establish or maintain our relationship with you, respond to your inquiries, provide you with services you have requested, keep you informed of services we think may be of interest to you, personalize your experience with us, and other reasons.Without PII, Tao of Wellness may be unable to provide you with the services you have requested. Disclosure of InformationTao of Wellness does not sell or lease PII about you to others.Tao of Wellness may share PII about you with others as permitted by contractual agreement or as required by law, such as our affiliates, third parties in connection with the provision of services to you, government entities and regulatory bodies, and those with whom you have requested us to share information.Unless restricted by law, regulation, contract or professional standards, Tao of Wellness may transfer PII about you outside of the United States to other countries for the purposes described in this privacy notice.Tao of Wellness will not share PII about you with an unaffiliated third party who is not performing services for us without first obtaining your permission, except if such sharing is otherwise permitted by this privacy notice.Tao of Wellness will provide PII about you to the following types of third parties for the associated reasons:Carriers: Tao of Wellness will provide your name and address to companies which provide a delivery service between Tao of Wellness and its customers as a means of delivering our products to you as quickly as possible.Financial Institutions: Tao of Wellness will provide financial institutions with your payment information, name, address, and phone number in order to process any orders placed by you and complete payment of the transaction to Tao of Wellness.Logistics: Tao of Wellness will provide your name, address and phone number to those entities or people within our network of distribution in order to process and ship your orders with speed and accuracy.Tao of Wellness requires third parties who perform services for us to agree to treat PII about you confidentially and securely. Prior to collection your PII, any such third parties are required to sign a service agreement, which includes the privacy policy outlined here.Notwithstanding any other provision of this notice or the Terms and Conditions of Use to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose and use your PII if we believe that we are required to do so: (a) by law; (b) in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena; (c) in response to a law enforcement agency’s request; (d) to enforce our other terms, conditions, or policies; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Tao of Wellness, you or others; and/or (g) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages we may sustain. For example, we may to the fullest extent the law allows, disclose PII about you to law enforcement agencies to assist them in identifying individuals who have been or may be engaged in unlawful activities.Because Non-PII does not personally identify you, we reserve the right to use Non-PII, and to disclose Non-PII to third parties, for any purpose.AccessYou may request access to the PII that Tao of Wellness has about you. You may also request the correction, amendment or deletion of PII about you that is inaccurate. Tao of Wellness will treat requests for access, correction, amendment or deletion of PII about you in accordance with its internal policies and applicable legal requirements.Information Security and IntegrityTao of Wellness maintains reasonable physical, administrative and technical safeguards to protect PII from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Our personnel and the personnel of our affiliates are provided access to PII about you only if they have a need to know the information in connection with a legitimate business purpose, such as (a) the provision of services to you or (b) to help identify other services that Tao of Wellness and its affiliates offer that may be of interest or use to you.Additionally, Tao of Wellness will only use PII for the purpose which it was intentionally collected. Tao of Wellness will take reasonable measures to safeguard your information and ensure that is accurate, complete and current. EnforcementTao of Wellness takes a self-assessment approach to verify that we are within compliance of this policy. Tao of Wellness employees are trained to adhere with this privacy policy and Tao of Wellness administers discipline to those employees who do not comply. Safe HarborIn order to comply with EU data privacy directives, Tao of Wellness applies the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework developed by the US Department of Commerce pertaining to the collection, use, and retention of personal information from the European Union member countries. Tao of Wellness complies with the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. For more information or questions concerning the Safe Harbor program please visit:  http://export.gov/safeharbor/index.aspIn compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Tao of Wellness commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information.  European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Tao of Wellness at the address provided in the questions section of this privacy policy.Tao of Wellness has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Tao of Wellness, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site atwww.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint. Changes to This Privacy NoticeTao of Wellness reserves the right to change this privacy notice. Any changes to this notice will become effective upon posting of the revised notice on the Internet or as required by law.QuestionsIf you have any questions or concerns regarding this notice, please contact us either by email at contact@taoofwellness.com, or by regular mail at Tao of Wellness, Inc., Attn: Legal Department, 2825 Santa Monica Blvd. Suite 300, Santa Monica, California, 90404.  Tao of Wellness will investigate and try to resolve any disputes regarding the use or disclosure of PII according to the principles of this privacy policy.Please note that email communications are not necessarily secure. Accordingly you should not include credit card information or other sensitive information in your email correspondence to us.
